(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
おめかし中...
Getting ready...
目覚まし起きた朝は
On the morning I woke up to my alarm,
なんだかいつもより眠くて
For some reason I was sleepier than usual.
昨日の夜ずっと
All last night,
漫画を読んでたら眠れなくなっちゃった
I was reading manga and couldn't fall asleep.
今頃そっちは
Over there right now,
どこで何してるかななんて
I wonder where you are and what you're doing.
考えてたら心が
Thinking about that, my heart
ふわっと軽くなるんだ
Feels light and airy.
これは内緒なんだけど
This is a secret, but
昨日読んだ漫画の
In the manga I read yesterday,
主人公に君が
The main character
ちょっと似てて驚いたんだよ
Looked a bit like you, and I was surprised.
ねぇ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に
Hey, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, together
食べよう
Let's eat!
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち 共有したくて
I just want to share the same feeling with you a bit.
そう お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 食べても
That's right, even if we eat lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch
何回でも いつもの君でいいんだよ
Any number of times, it's okay just to be your usual self.
一緒に食べよう
Let's eat together!
隠し味はずっと
The secret ingredient is always
言えない地味な秘密だけど
A simple secret I can't tell, but
サラダも最近は
Even the salads lately
少しキラキラなんだ
Have been a bit sparkly.
こんなに突然に
Even if something bad
嫌なことあっても
Happens so suddenly,
君に会えると思うとニヤけちゃってさ
I can't help but grin when I think I can see you.
ねぇ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に
Hey, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, together
食べよう
Let's eat!
一人よりきっと楽しくなるから
Because it'll surely be more fun than being alone.
そう お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 食べ出し
That's right, starting to eat lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch
正解なんてないから 変なこと考えないでよ
There's no right answer, so don't think about weird things.
まぁ 別にけど
Well, not that I mind, but...
溢れる
Overflowing...
言葉 ひとつ ひとつ
Words, one by one...
嬉しくなったり 楽しくなったり
Getting happy, getting fun...
不思議なパワーを感じる
I feel a mysterious power...
ってこと
...is what I mean.
ねぇ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に
Hey, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, together
食べよう
Let's eat!
ひる ひる ひる ひる 食べよう
Lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, let's eat!
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち共有したくて
I just wanted to share the same feeling for a bit
そうひる ひる ひる ひる ひる ひる 誰でも
Yes, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, anyone
とっておきのことじゃなくても
Even if it's not something special
いつでも君がいるんだよ
You're always there
一緒に食べよう
Let's eat together
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
1曲目、『Lunch with me』をお聞きいただきました！ありがとう！
You just heard the first song, 'Lunch with me'! Thank you!
というわけで、みんな、こんねねー！
So, hello everyone, Kon-nene!
わあー！こんねね、こんねね、こんねねー！
Wow! Kon-nene, Kon-nene, Kon-nene!
ホロライブ5期生、オレンジ担当の、桃鈴ねねです！よろしくねー！
I'm Momosuzu Nene, the orange representative of Hololive's 5th generation! Nice to meet you!
というわけで、皆さん、今日はねねのYouTubeの無料のソロライブ、『ねねいろらいぶ』にお越しいただきまして、皆様、本当にありがとうございます！イエーイ！
So everyone, thank you so much for coming to Nene's free solo live on YouTube, 'Nene-iro Live'! Yay!
ちょっと待ってね。
Wait a moment.
うー、高速ミス。
Ugh, high-speed mistake.
ただいま。よいしょ。
I'm back. There we go.
はい、というわけで、今日がですね、『Lunch with me』の完成版のダンスのお披露目だったんですけれども、
Yes, so today was the debut of the final version of the dance for 'Lunch with me', but...
ちょっとね、何か所かちょっと間違えちゃった気もするけど、どうでしたでしょうか？
I feel like I might have messed up in a few places, but how was it?
コメント、コメント。
Comments, comments.
あ、可愛い、あ、めっちゃ可愛い、吐息ASMR助かる。ありがとう！
Ah, cute! Ah, so cute! "Panting ASMR is a lifesaver". Thank you!
はい、みんな、今日はですね、ハッシュタグ『#ねねいろらいぶ』。
All right, everyone, today's hashtag is '#NeneiroRaibu'.
普段からねねが配信タグとして使ってるタグが、今日のライブのタグになりますので、よかったらたくさんツイートしてね！
The tag I usually use for my streams is the tag for today's live, so please tweet a lot!
はい、というわけで、ねねの息もだいぶ落ち着いてきましたので、2曲目に行きたいと思います！
All right, my breathing has settled down a bit, so I'd like to move on to the second song!
というわけで、聴いてください。冒険でしょでしょ？
So, please listen. Bouken Desho Desho?
答えはいつも私の胸に
The answer is always in my heart
何でだろう あなたを選んだ私です
I wonder why... it was me who chose you
もう止まらない 運命様から決められたけど
I can't stop now, even if it was decided by fate
I believe 真似だけじゃつまらないのよ
I believe, just imitating is boring
You be light!! 感じるまま感じることだけを するよ
You be light!! I'll just feel what I feel
冒険でしょでしょ！？ホントがウソに変わる世界で
It's an adventure, right!? In a world where truth turns to lies
夢があるから強くなるのよ 誰のためじゃない
Because I have a dream, I become strong, and it's not for anyone else's sake
一緒に来てください どこまでも自由な
Please come with me, to where we can be infinitely free
私を見てよね 明日過去になった今日の今が奇跡
Look at me, okay? Today, which becomes the past tomorrow, is a miracle
I believe you...
戻れない どこまで行かなきゃつまんない
I can't go back, it's boring if I don't go far
さあ教えて 秘めてる願いを鏡に投げた
Now tell me, I threw my hidden wish into the mirror
My delight!! 体ごと受け止めたら
My delight!! If I take it all in with my whole body
Your my flight!! 驚かせて驚いて笑顔に なろう
Your my flight!! Let's surprise and be surprised and smile
始まりでしょでしょ！？キレイな闇を照らすみたいに
It's the beginning, right!? Like lighting up the beautiful darkness
私のチカラ あなたの涙のち晴れにしよう
My power, let's turn your tears into clear skies
現実に揺れる 繊細な心が傷つくのはイヤ
I don't want my delicate heart, wavering in reality, to be hurt
思いましたいつもいつも胸の奥に
I always, always thought about it deep in my heart
答えが
The answer
普通じゃないのが当然なら
If it's only natural to be out of the ordinary
答える私は何ができる？
Then what can I do in response?
普通でも普通じゃなくて
Even if I'm normal, I'm not normal
感じるまま感じることだけをするよ
I'll just do whatever I feel, as I feel it
もう冒険でしょでしょ？ 本当か嘘に変わる世界で
It's an adventure already, right? In a world where truth turns to lies
夢があるから強くなるのよ 誰のためじゃない
Because I have a dream, I become strong, and not for anyone else's sake
始まりでしょ？ 始まりなんでしょ？
It's a beginning, right? It's the beginning, isn't it?
綺麗な闇を照らすみたいに
Like lighting up a beautiful darkness
私とあなた 冒険の途中
You and I are in the middle of an adventure
一緒に進んでこう
Let's move forward together
どこまでも自由に 現実も越えて
Free to go anywhere, even beyond reality
明日過去になった今日の今が奇跡
This moment of today, which will be the past tomorrow, is a miracle
確かな未来を
A certain future
掴もう
Let's grasp it
未来を
The future
I Celebrate You
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
えー、『冒険でしょでしょ？』お聴きしました！
That was "Bouken Desho Desho?"!
えーというわけで、ちょっと先にね、ステージの移動はしたいと思いますので、
And with that, I'd like to move to the next stage,
移動したいと思います！
so I'm going to head over there now!
レッツ...
Let's...
と思ったけども、ちょっと時間待ってたわ。
Actually, I have to wait a little bit first.
えー、『冒険でしょでしょ？』お聴きいただきました。
You just heard "Bouken Desho Desho?."
えーとね、3Dライブの... 3Dお披露目の時に一曲ね、
Um, during my 3D debut live,
『涼宮ハルヒ』から一曲歌ったんですけど、
I sang a song from "Haruhi Suzumiya,"
今回もね、もう一曲歌いたいなと思って
so I wanted to sing another one this time,
『冒険でしょでしょ？』選んでみました。
and I chose "Bouken Desho Desho?."
みんな知ってましたか？
Did you guys know it?
あ、ねね、この曲大好き！ イエーイ！
I love this song so much! Yay!
はい、じゃあというわけでね、先にステージ移動したいと思います！
Alright, then, let's head to the next stage!
移動！
Moving!
あ、来た来た来た！ よかった！
Oh, here we go! Thank goodness!
あねねの声聞こえる？ みんな。
Can you all hear me?
あーどうもどうも。
Ah, hello, hello.
あ、知ってた？ めっちゃ懐かしい。本当？
Ah, you knew it? It brings back so many memories. Really?
あねね結構現役選手なんだけど。困ったな。
I'm still a pro at this, though. Oh boy.
ちょっとね、ここでね、えーとフリートークの時間取ってもいいっていうことだったので、
They said I could have some free talk time here,
前回ね、えーと3Dお披露目の時にはできなかったこの桜並木ステージで
so I wanted to hold a photoshoot with all the Nekkos
ねっ子の皆とちょっと撮影会をしたいと思ってますので、
on this cherry blossom stage, which I couldn't do during my 3D debut.
ちょっとねっ子、いる？ いるかな？
So, any Nekkos here? Are you around?
あれ？ あれ、ねっ子の皆さーん、ねっ... あ、いた！
Huh? Hey, Nekko friends... Oh, there you are!
いるじゃん！ うぇい！
You're here! Yay!
あ、ちょっとハンドパワーになっちゃう。
Wait, it looks like I'm using magic powers.
あ、ハンドパワーになっちゃう。イエーイ！
Ah, magic powers! Yay!
あ、ちょっとこっちの子上手く持ってるから人参の子にしよっかな。
Oh, this one's easier to hold, so I'll go with the carrot one.
あ、やだ、ちょっと待ってよ。んー。
Oh no, hold on. Hmm.
なんか、あれ待って、あねね顔面ガシッてやってない？
Wait, am I grabbing the Nekko's face?
ねっ子の皆の、ガシガシ、ガシガシ。
Grabbing you guys, scritch, scritch.
あーそっか、今日は透けるタイプなのなんだ。スケルトンなんだね。
Oh, I see, you're the transparent type today. You're a skeleton!
あ、そっかそっか。撮れた？ みんな。
Oh, right, right. Did you get the shot, everyone?
あ、今日はちょっと透け... あ、あ、これで、みんな！
Oh, today you're a bit... Ah, there we go, everyone!
あ、これで撮って。あ、すごい良いじゃん。
Take a photo of this. Oh, that looks great.
あのセクシーアングルと共に。
With a sexy angle.
あ、ラミィ！ モンハン頑張ってる？
Ah, Lamy! Working hard at Monster Hunter?
はい、わき。
Here's my armpit.
あーどうもどうも。あ、アップどうもアップどうも。
Ah, hello, hello. Oh, thanks for the close-up, thanks.
あーラミィが喜んじゃう。あーどうもみんな撮れた？
Lamy's going to love this. Did you all get the shot?
あ、出た出た。浮いててくれてありがとね。ごめんね。
Oh, there you are. Thanks for floating. Sorry about that.
乗れる？
Can you hop on?
あ、いいじゃん！ かわいい！
Oh, that's great! So cute!
あ、かわいい！ あ、めっちゃいい感じ！
Oh, cute! This feels really good!
さっさっさっ
Swish, swish, swish
ちょっとね、ちょっと風送るからさ。いい？行くよ。
Wait a bit, I'm going to send some breeze your way. Ready? Here I go.
ふーー！
Wheee!
ふーー！！
Wheee!!
あ、帰ってきた
Oh, it came back.
ふーー！
Wheee!
ふーー！！
Wheee!!
いい感じみんな。撮れた？
Looking good, everyone. Did you get the shot?
どうですか？
How is it?
こんなのとか、
How about this,
or this,
こんなのとか。
or even this.
もう撮り放題！
Take as many as you want!
あ、助かる。
Ah, that's helpful.
あ、全身斜めのアングル助かる。
Ah, a full-body diagonal angle is great.
あ、なんてセクシーなんだ。素晴らしい。
Oh, how sexy. Wonderful.
あ、やっぱ、あ、違うな。
Ah, as expected... no, it's different.
やっぱプロのカメラマンさん違うな、やっぱ。わかってるわ、ねねのセクシーな角度。
A professional cameraman really is different. He knows Nene's sexy angles.
最高！ありがとうございます。
The best! Thank you very much.
ねっ子のみんなもありがとう。
Nekkos, thank you all too.
よしよし。じゃあね、準備が整ったということで、
Alright, alright. Since everything is ready now,
えー次の曲に行きたいと思います。
I'd like to move on to the next song.
えー、次の曲はですね、
The next song is...
ちょっとこの桜並木に合わせて、しっとりとした曲をお送りしたいと思います。
I'd like to perform a mellow song to match these cherry blossom trees.
過去のねねの歌枠で一度だけ登場したことのある曲です。
It's a song that has only appeared once in Nene's past singing streams.
えー、それでは聞いてください。Everything。
Now, please listen. Everything.
Everything
作詞:MISIA 作曲:松本俊明
Lyrics: MISIA, Composition: Toshiaki Matsumoto
すれ違う時の中で
In the midst of passing time
あなたと巡り会えた
I was able to encounter you
不思議ね 願った奇跡が
It's mysterious, isn't it? The miracle I wished for...
こんなにもそばにあるなんて
is actually so close to me
会いたい思いのまま
With the same desire to see you
会えない時間だけが
only the time we can't meet...
過ぎてく扉すり抜けて
passes through the door
また思い出して あの人と笑いあうあなたを
And I remember again, you laughing with that person
愛しき人よ 悲しませないで
Oh beloved one, please don't make me sad
泣き疲れて 眠る夜もあるから
Because there are nights I fall asleep tired of crying
過去を見ないで 見つめて 私だけ
Don't look at the past, look only at me
You're everything
あなたが想うより強く
Stronger than you think
優しい嘘ならいらない
I don't need gentle lies
欲しいのはあなた
What I want is you
Oh... Oh... yeah
どれくらいの時間を
How much time...
永遠と呼べるだろう
can we call eternity?
果てしなく遠い未来なら
If it's the endless, distant future...
あなたと行きたい あなたと覗いてみたい
I want to go with you, I want to peek into it with you
Oh na na na...
愛しき人よ 抱きしめていて
Oh beloved one, please hold me close
いつものように 優しい時の中で
Just like always, in a gentle time
この手握って 見つめて
Hold this hand and look at me
今だけを
Only at this moment
You're everything You're everything
あなたと 離れてる場所でも
Even when I'm apart from you
会えばきっと 許してしまう
If we meet, I'm sure I'll forgive you
どんな 夜でも
No matter what kind of night it is
You're everything You're everything
あなたの 夢見るほど強く
As strongly as I dream of you
愛せる力を勇気に
Turning the power to love into courage
今変えて行こう
Let's change it now
あ、間違えちゃった！
Ah, I made a mistake!
You're everything You're everything
あなたと 離れてる場所でも
Even when I'm apart from you
会えばいつも 消え去って行く
Whenever we meet, they always fade away
胸の 痛みも
Even the pain in my chest
You're everything You're everything
あなたが 想うより強く
More strongly than you think
優しい嘘なら いらない
I don't need gentle lies
欲しいのは あなた
The one I want is you
You're everything You're everything
You're everything My everything
あーっははははは！
Ah-hahahaha!
大変だ、みんな、間違えちゃってよ。
Oh no, everyone, I made a mistake.
この曲、あの「Every thing」っていう発音が
In this song, the pronunciation of "Every thing"
そもそもちょっとねねにはね、だいぶあの、あの、難しくて。
was originally a bit, well, quite difficult for Nene.
ちょっと難易度高かったわ。
The difficulty level was a bit high.
これからも練習したいと思います。
I'll keep on practicing it.
マッスル、マッスル！
Muscle, muscle!
はい、というわけで、えっと、待って。
Alright then, um, wait.
間違えたことで緊張度が上がって、何もわかんなくなしてきちゃったので、
Making a mistake made me more nervous, and I've started losing track of things,
お水飲んで落ち着きます。
so I'll drink some water and calm down.
あー。よしよし。よしよし。オッケー、オッケー。
Ah. All right. All right. Okay, okay.
よし、というわけで、じゃあね。
Alright, so anyway.
今はすごいあの、エモエモな感じの曲を聴いてもらったので。
Just now you heard a very emotional kind of song.
ちょっとエモくなったかどうか微妙なんだけど。
Though I'm not sure if it actually felt emotional.
次はね、あの「ザ・アイドル！」みたいな曲を、
Next, I'm going to perform a song that's like,
この桜並木のステージで、あの、披露したいと思います！
"The Idol!" here on this cherry blossom stage!
イェーイ、イェーイ、イェーイ！
Yay, yay, yay!
アイドルっぽい曲って何かなーって思ったときに、
When I was thinking about what an idol-like song is,
昔ねねが見てたアニメで、あの、めちゃめちゃアイドルしてる子がいて。
there was a girl in an anime I used to watch who was a total idol.
その子の曲をちょっと今回はお借りして、えー、歌っていきたいと思いますので、
I'm going to borrow her song this time and sing it,
よかったら皆さん聴いてください。
so please listen to it if you like.
というわけで、次の曲、えー、「ハッピークレセント」！
So, the next song is... "Happy Crescent"!
ハッピークレセント
Happy Crescent
黒板そっちのけで
Ignoring the blackboard
チラリ見つめる先は
Where my eyes glance is
甘い予感がファンタジー
A sweet premonition, it's fantasy
全校舎の裏
Behind the whole school building
そぼたれる愛もど
Drenched in a love-like state
やっぱ私にゃ邪魔いい
It's just too much of a bother for me
だけどあなたの為に頑張る
But I'll do my best for you
いつの日にか振り向かせてみせるわ！
One day, I'll make you look my way!
鈍感すぎやロミオさん
You're too insensitive, Mr. Romeo
ハピハピハッピープレゼント
Happy happy happy present
あなたにハッピープレゼント
A happy present for you
分かって欲しいのこの気持ち
I want you to understand these feelings
あなただけよエーロマンス
It's only you, A-romance
ハピハピハッピープレゼント
Happy happy happy present
あなたに全部捧げるアイラブユー
I'll give you everything, I love you
いつか終わるの？ねえ抱きしめて欲しい
When will it end? Hey, I want you to hold me
片想い
Unrequited love
まとめ溜息色
Gathered up in the color of a sigh
ついに見つめる先に
At the end of my gaze at last
暗い横顔ミステリー
Your dark profile is a mystery
走る渡り廊下 背中失恋モード
Running through the hallway, your back in heartbreak mode
もしかして振られたの？
Wait, did you get rejected?
元気出してよ 私がいるよ
Cheer up, I'm right here
告白だよ でも気づいてない顔
It's a confession, but you have that oblivious look
鈍感すぎやロミオさん
You're too insensitive, Mr. Romeo
トキメキハッピープレゼント
Heart-throbbing happy present
ドキドキもっとプレゼント
Giving you more heart-pounding presents
気づいて欲しいの胸の鼓動
I want you to notice my heart's thumping
奏でてるよ恋のメロディ
Playing a melody of love
トキメキハッピープレゼント
Heart-throbbing happy present
あなたに全部捧げるアイウォンチュー
I'll give you everything, I want you
いつになるだろ？ ねえ終わらせたいよ
When will it be? Hey, I want to end this
片想い
Unrequited love
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
ハッピープレゼント 楽しんでくれてましたかー！
Did you enjoy Happy Gift?!
ロミオさん
Mr. Romeo
ハピハピハッピープレゼント
Happy happy happy present
あなたにハッピープレゼント
A happy present for you
分かって欲しいのこの気持ち
I want you to understand these feelings
あなただけよエーロマンス
It's only you, A-romance
ハピハピハッピープレゼント
Happy happy happy present
あなたに全部捧げるアイラブユー
I'll give you everything, I love you
いつか終わるの？ねえ抱きしめて欲しい
When will it end? Hey, I want you to hold me
せーの！ 片想い
One, two... Unrequited love!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
えー、ハッピープレゼントという曲を
Uh, the song Happy Gift...
お聞きいただき... 聞いていただきましたー！
You listened to... You listened to it!
ちょっと待ってね、お水...
Wait a second, water...
なー。いやいや、もう。ちょっとみんなにはね、
Whew. No no, really. I think to everyone,
あのほら、元気なねねしか見えてないと思うけど
you know, only energetic Nene is visible, but
もうねね、汗びっしょ！
Nene is already drenched in sweat!
びそびそー。でもまだまだ頑張れますので、
Soaking wet. But I can still keep going,
頑張ります！
so I'll do my best!
えーっと。よいしょよいしょ。
Um. Heave-ho, heave-ho.
えー次は、えーじゃあ、夕方。
Uh next, uh well, evening.
昼の部ときて、夕方の部ときたら、
We had the afternoon part, then the evening part,
次はなんと！ 夜の部ですね！
so next is none other than! The night part!
というわけでステージ移動したいと思うんですけど、
So, I’d like to move stages, but
なんとね、夜の部、1箇所、
actually, for the night part, one spot
前回から変わったところがあるらしいので、
seems to have changed since last time,
皆さんそれも、えー探しながら、
so please, uh, look for it
えーお楽しみください。
while you enjoy yourselves.
というわけで、夜の部へ移動ー！
And with that, let’s move to the night part!
惑星ループ
Planet Loop
銀河の隅で 惑星はぐるぐる回る
In a corner of the galaxy, the planet spins around and around
電波の記録 エコーが返ってきた これで何回だ
A recording of radio waves, an echo came back. How many times is this now?
これで何回だ
How many times is this now?
遠くの空で あなたに恋をしたんだ
In the distant sky, I fell in love with you
届かないこと わかっているのに
Even though I know I won't reach you
ああ あなたに会いたいな って気持ちがループループする
Ah, my feelings of "I want to see you" loop and loop
頭がどうにかなりそうだ それ以外交わせない
My head feels like it's going to go crazy, I can't exchange anything else
ああ 今すぐ会いたいな って理屈もループループする
Ah, the logic of "I want to see you right now" also loops and loops
この周回軌道上に あなたがいなくても
Even if you aren't on this orbit
そこに大体愛があるだけ
There is mostly just love there
声を辿って 何光年 延長線に消えてゆく
Following the voice, it disappears many light-years away on the extension line
このままパッと 忘れられたら 楽だろうな
It would be easier if I could just forget everything like this
触れられないのに 見えてしまって どうしようもないやいや
I can't touch you, but I can see you, and there's nothing I can do
近くで遠い あなただって わかってるよ
I know you're near yet far
ああ それでも会いたいな って何度もループループする
Ah, but I still want to see you, looping over and over again
心があなたで鳴っている それだけが確かだ
My heart is ringing for you, that's the only certain thing
それだけでいいよ
That's enough for me
ああ こっちが回るように 僕らはずっとループする
Ah, so that this side turns, we loop forever
想いが軌道を描いている あなただけを追うよ
My thoughts are drawing an orbit, I'll only follow you
ああ 今すぐ会いたいな って命がループループする
Ah, my life loops and loops with the feeling of "I want to see you right now"
この周回軌道上に あなたがいなくても
Even if you aren't on this orbit
それ以外思えない
I can't think of anything else
そこに大体愛があるだけ
There is mostly just love there
あーちょっと、みんなちょっと、タイム
Ah, wait... everyone... time out for a second
タイム見ないで今
Don't look at the time right now
うわあ！
Waa!
はいオッケー、カメラマンさんオッケーです。
Okay, the cameraman is ready.
はい、ねねです。
Hi, it's Nene.
はいということで、惑星ループお聞きいただきました。
And so, you just heard 'Wakusei Loop'.
イエーイ！
Yay!
この曲ね、あのー、凄くずっと飛んでるからね。
That song, you know, involves a lot of jumping.
あのー、心臓がめっちゃもう、あのー、ちょっとたま…
My heart is really... well, it's a bit...
お心臓が心臓ってなるんだ、この曲。
My heart really goes 'ba-dump ba-dump' with this song.
でも凄く楽しい曲でしょ、惑星ループ。
But it's such a fun song, isn't it? 'Wakusei Loop'.
なんかね、この動きとっても簡単だし、みんなもね、
The moves are very simple, so I think...
あのー真似しやすいんじゃないかな。
...it's easy for everyone to copy them.
今後ねねがまた歌う機会があったら、
If Nene has a chance to sing it again,
みんなクルクルクルクル回っててね。
please spin around and around with me.
はい、えーということでですね、あのー次がね、
Okay, so, the next one is...
今回、今回のライブであのー最大級に踊りが忙しい曲と
...the most dance-intensive song in this whole live performance.
なりますので、ちょっとねねは息を整えてから、
So I'm going to catch my breath for a moment...
えー次に行きたいと思います。
...before moving on to the next one.
あ、そうだみんな、あのーステージのさ、変わったところさ、
Oh, right! Did everyone notice the change on the stage?
分かったみんな？
Did you catch it?
あ、ねねに夢中で、みんなあのー分かってなかったでしょ正直。
Ah, you were so mesmerized by Nene that you didn't notice, honestly.
ねねばっか見てたでしょ、スクショしてたでしょ。
You were just looking at Nene, taking screenshots, weren't you?
ステージ分かった人？
Did anyone notice the stage?
どこだったと思う？
Where do you think it was?
えーっと、深呼吸が今までと違う？
Hmm? My deep breaths are different from before?
それはねねが疲れてるだけだよみんな。
That's just because Nene is tired, guys.
分からなかった？でしょーでしょー？
You didn't know? See, told you!
じゃあちょっと、あのーねねのこの上の方に注目してください。
Then, please pay attention to the area above me.
ドンドンドンドーン！
Boom boom boom boom!
え、見て。これ見て分かるみんな、何が違うか。
Look. Can you tell what's different?
なんと、なんとこの「SUPER NENECHI STAGE」って書いてある
Believe it or not, this sign that says 'SUPER NENECHI STAGE'...
看板みたいなところが、あのーピカピカになりました！
...is now all shiny and lit up!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ありがとう！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you so much!
なんか前回お披露目の時は間に合わなくて、
It wasn't ready in time for the last showcase,
あのー今日、今日に間に合うようにね、あのーめちゃくちゃ頑張ってくれました。
but they worked incredibly hard to have it ready for today.
ありがとうございます。大感謝！
Thank you very much. Deepest thanks!
やったー！ほら見て引きで見た時ね、全然あのーSuper Nenechi感が違うでしょ。
Yay! Look, when you see it from a distance, the 'Super Nenechi' vibe is totally different.
はい、ということで、ねねの息整いましたので、
All right then, I've caught my breath,
次の曲に行きたいと思います。
so I'd like to move on to the next song.
みんな大好きハニワさんの曲から一曲歌いたいと思います。
I'm going to sing a song by HoneyWorks that everyone loves.
それでは聴いてください。ヒロイン育成計画。
Please listen to 'Heroine Ikusei Keikaku'.
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で 王子様にちやほやされるんでしょ？
If I were a heroine, I'd surely be beautiful and pampered by a prince, right?
芋女の私も お姫様になれたら なんてね
If a plain girl like me could also become a princess... just kidding!
イエーイ！
Yay!
バイト探し 採用ないし
Looking for a part-time job, but no one's hiring me.
ヤケになって飛び込む 場違いすぎる世界
In desperation, I dive into a world where I'm completely out of place.
走りばかり 雑…あ、ちょっと待って！
Always running, miscel... Ah, wait a second!
あ、ちょっとスタッフさんストップ！
Ah, staff, please stop!
ねねの所、何も聞こえなくなっちゃった。
I can't hear anything in my ears anymore.
ストップ音楽！
Music, stop!
うわー、もう一回やりたい！うわー。
Ugh, I want to do it again! Ugh.
止まった？何も聞こえなくなった。
Did it stop? I couldn't hear a thing.
おれ？助けてー！
Huh? Help me!
ありゃりゃりゃりゃ。何かが…あ、ごめんねみんな、ちょっとほら
Oopsie-daisy. Something's... Ah, sorry everyone.
ねねがポーズ取ってるから、それ見ててよ。
I'll strike some poses, so just watch me for a bit.
トラブルはつきもんだよな、みんな。イエーイ、イエーイ。
Troubles are part of the game, right guys? Yay, yay.
ねねのダンスが激しすぎて、あのーマイクがついてこれなくなった、
My dancing was so intense that the mic couldn't keep up.
こりゃ。困ったぜ。
Geez, what a mess.
やっぱスーパーねねち一味違うわ、みんな。アップで見ちゃってねねのこと。
As expected, Super Nenechi is just on another level. Take a close look at me.
ドヤ見、ほら、未鑑定の脇。
Feast your eyes, look, my unidentifiable armpits.
よし、ちょっとこれを機にちょっと休憩にしようか。よいしょ、お水飲もう。
Alright, let's take this chance to have a little break. Time for some water.
あ、やだ、ちょっとネタバレしちゃったじゃんみんなにダンス。よいしょ。
Oh no, I accidentally spoiled the dance for you all. There we go.
おいしい。あ、聞こえる聞こえる。うん。
Tastes good. Ah, I can hear it now. Yeah.
よしよし、えーっとスタッフさん、BGMが非常に小さく、
Okay, okay. Um, staff, the background music is very quiet,
ねねの声が非常に大きいという状況になっております。
and my voice is extremely loud.
よし、オッケー、オッケーだみんな。お待たせしました。
Alright, it's okay now, guys. Sorry to keep you waiting.
お待たせ、みんな。
Sorry everyone.
あ、ちょっと待ってな、ねねの耳に入ってくる声が、
Ah, wait a second, the volume in my ear is...
莫大、莫大、バクバク代々だ。
...huge, huge, absolutely enormous.
あ、あ、あ、もう一個大きくがい。
Ah, ah, ah, make it one level louder.
あ、あ、よしよし。
Ah, ah, alright.
あ、あ、あ、あ…
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
あ、ありがとうございます。
Ah, thank you.
あ、いい感じ。
Ah, it's looking good.
よし。
Alright.
あ、どうする？
Ah, what should I do?
どうやって立て直すみんな？えー…
How should I get back into it, everyone? Uhm...
イェーイ！
Yay!
それでは次は、えー、みんなが、えー、
And now, for the next one, uhm...
大好きなあのハニワさんから一曲歌わせていただきたいと思います。
I'd like to sing a song from the HoneyWorks that everyone loves.
それでは、えー、さっきの曲はみんなあのぶっ飛ばしていただいて…
Now then, uhm, please put that last song out of your minds...
それでは、ヒロイン育成計画、聴いてください。
Now then, please listen to "Heroine Training Program."
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で 王子様にちやほやされるんでしょ
If I were a heroine, I'd surely be beautiful and pampered by a prince, right?
芋女の私も お姫様になれたらなんてね、イェーイ！
Even an unrefined girl like me wishes I could become a princess... just kidding! Yay!
ヒロイン育成計画
Heroine Training Program
才当探し採用なし
Searching for talent, none recruited.
やけになって飛び込む 間違いすぎる世界
Diving headfirst into a world that's just too wrong.
他尻埃雑用係
Cleaning up after others, just a chore girl.
最悪な奴らの マネージャー就任です
I've become the manager for the worst guys ever.
バレたら最後
If I'm found out, it's the end.
目立たれるの嫌だし 生きるためだし
I hate standing out, but it's to survive.
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で 王子様にちやほやされるんでしょ
If I were a heroine, I'd surely be beautiful and pampered by a prince, right?
芋女の私も お姫様になれたらなんてね
Even an unrefined girl like me wishes I could become a princess... just kidding!
私をプロデュースして 髪も服も全部可愛くして
Produce me, make my hair and clothes all cute.
いつか出会う王子様 どこで何をしてるの神様
The prince I'll meet someday, where is he and what's he doing, oh God?
待ってますから気長に はー！
I'll wait patiently, hah!
ある日出会う 運命の人
One day I'll meet the person of destiny.
紳士な振る舞いに ドキドキしちゃったんだ
My heart skipped a beat at his gentlemanly behavior.
名前なんて 聞けるはずない
There's no way I could ask for his name.
また会いたいなんて 願ってるだけでした
I was just wishing I could meet him again.
時間が止まる
Time stops.
また会えたねと君に やっぱり恋だ
I saw you again and said, "We met again," it's definitely love.
きっと少女漫画じゃ両思い ベタでいいじゃんむしろベタがいいじゃん
In a girls' comic, our love would surely be mutual; clichés are fine, in fact, I prefer them!
モブ女の私も ヒロインなる気ありますなんてね
Even a background girl like me has what it takes to be a heroine... just kidding!
すぐにくっついちゃえばいい 悲劇いらないシェイクスピア
We should just get together right away; no need for tragedies, Shakespeare.
やっと会えた王子様 まずは名前を知るとこだよね
The prince I finally met, first I need to find out his name, right?
ヒロインらしく自然に バレちゃった最悪な奴らに
Acting naturally like a heroine... but those worst guys found me out!
バレちゃったダメだ 100%振られるってどうすればいいの
They found me out, it's no good! I'm 100% going to be rejected, what should I do?
イェーイ！ワッショイ！
Yay! Wasshoi!
気持ちなら負けないなんて みんなおんなじこと思ってて
Saying my feelings won't lose... everyone thinks the same thing.
そこからの勇気と 押しが大事なんです聞いてる？
From there, courage and persistence are what matter, are you listening?
ヒロインなら綺麗で 王子様にちやほやされるんでしょ
If I were a heroine, I'd surely be beautiful and pampered by a prince, right?
芋女の私も お姫様になれるのなんてね
Even an unrefined girl like me could become a princess... just kidding!
自信ちょっとついたよ
I've gained a little confidence.
当たって砕けたら 馬鹿にして笑ってよお願い
If I crash and burn, please just make fun of me and laugh.
行ってきますね告白 よし！
I'm going now, time to confess. Alright!
ヒロインになれ今日から
Become a heroine starting today.
わぁ、おっけー…わぁ…はい…はい…はい…おべべ…よいしょ。
Wow, okay... wow... yes... yes... yes... phew... heave-ho.
あー…ちょっとあのみんな ねねあの 鼻水 鼻のウォーターの方が…
Ah... uhm everyone, Nene's, uhm, nose water... my "nose water" has...
鼻のウォーターの方が、あのウォーターしてしまって
Well, it's started "watering" a bit.
ちょっと今からあの「チーン」をしたいと思いますのであの…
So I'm going to go blow my nose now, so uhm...
オッケー、お待たせしました！
Okay, sorry to keep you waiting!
あ、ど最後の方さ...
Ah, right at the very end...
やべーやべー見えちゃう。
Oh no, oh no, you can see.
待って、危なかったー。
Wait, that was close!
はい、というわけで、『ヒロイン育成計画』をお聞きいただきました！
Alright, so that was "Heroine Ikusei Keikaku"!
ま、みんな記憶にないと思うけどね。あ、おまけで2回も歌っちゃった！ありがとう！
Well, I'm sure none of you remember it, though.
Ah, I sang it twice as a bonus! Thank you!
はい！というわけで、あのですね、今回はこのステージで終わりじゃなくって...
Yes! So, you see, it's not ending
on this stage this time...
ねねがね、今まで1回も立ったことのないステージで...
On a stage that Nene has
never stood on before...
今回は最後に2曲、歌わせていただきたいと思います！
I'd like to sing the last two songs there!
えーというわけで、移動したいと思います！
And with that, I'm going to move!
ホロアリーナへ、レッツゴー！
To the Holo Arena, let's go!
桃鈴ねね Momosuzu Nene / Nene Ch.
Momosuzu Nene / Nene Ch.
まだこの世界は
This world still seems to...
僕を飼いならしてたいみたいだ
...want to keep me tamed
スパークル 作詞 作曲 野田洋次郎
Sparkle
Lyrics/Composition: Yojiro Noda
望み通りだろう？
Just as you wished, right?
美しくもがくよ
I'll struggle beautifully
互いの砂時計
Let's share a kiss while...
眺めながらキスをしようよ
...watching each other's hourglasses
「さよなら」から一番遠い
Let's meet at a place...
場所で待ち合わせよう
...that's furthest from "goodbye"
ついに時は来た
Finally, the time has come
昨日までは序章の序章で
Until yesterday, it was just the prologue of prologues
飛ばし読みでいいから
You can just skim through it...
ここからが僕だよ
...because from here on is the real me
経験と知識と
With experience, knowledge...
カビの生えかかった勇気を持って
...and a courage that's started to gather mold
いまだかつてないスピードで
At a speed never seen before...
君のもとへダイブを
...I'll dive towards you
まどろみの中で 生温いコーラに
In a slumber, over a lukewarm cola...
ここではないどこかを夢みたよ
...I dreamed of a place other than here
教室の窓の外に
Outside the classroom window...
電車に揺られ運ばれる朝に
...in the morning as I'm carried, swaying on the train
運命だとか未来だとか
Words like "fate" or "future"...
って言葉がどれだけ手を
...no matter how far we stretch out our hands...
伸ばそうと届かない
...they can't reach that place...
場所で僕ら恋をする
...where we fall in love
時計の針も二人を
Even the hands of the clock...
時計の針も二人も
Even the clock hands and the two of us
横目に見ながら進む
We move forward while looking sideways at them
そんな世界を二人で一生
In such a world, the two of us, forever
いや、何章でも生き抜いていこう
No, let's live through as many chapters as it takes
「はじめまして」なんてさ
Words like "Nice to meet you"
遥か彼方へと追いやっ て
Let's banish them far away
千年周期を
Let's make a thousand-year cycle
一日で息しよう
Breathe in just one day
辞書にある言葉で
With words found in a dictionary
出来上がった世界を憎んだ
I hated the world that was made up
万華鏡の中で
Within a kaleidoscope
八月のある朝
One morning in August
君は僕の前で
In front of me, you
ハニかんでは澄ましてみせた
Shyly tried to look composed
この世界の教科書
Like a textbook of this world
のような笑顔で
With a smile like that
嘘みたいな日々を 規格外の意味を
Days like a lie, meanings out of the ordinary
悲劇だっていいから 望んだよ
I wished for it, even if it's a tragedy
そしたらドアの外に
Then, outside the door
君が全部抱えて立ってたよ
You were standing there, holding everything
運命だとか未来だとかって言葉が どれだけ手を伸ばそうと届かない
No matter how far words like "fate" or "future" reach, they can't get to
場所で僕ら恋をする
The place where we fall in love
愛し方さえも 君の匂いがした
Even the way of loving smelled like you
歩き方さえも その笑い声がした
Even the way of walking sounded like your laughter
いつか消えてなくなる 君のすべてを
Everything about you that will one day vanish
この目に焼き付けておくことは もう権利なんかじゃない
Keeping it burned into my eyes is no longer a right
義務だと思うんだ
I think it's a duty
運命だとか未来だとか
Words like fate or future
って言葉がどれだけ手を 伸ばそうと届かない
No matter how far they reach, they can't get to
場所で僕ら恋をする
The place where we fall in love
時計の針も二人も
Even the clock hands and the two of us
横目に見ながら進む
We move forward while looking sideways at them
そんな世界を二人で一生
In such a world, the two of us, forever
いや、何章でも生き抜いていこう
No, let's live through as many chapters as it takes
みんな、今はとってもいろんなことがあって辛い時期かと思いますが
Everyone, I think right now is a painful time with a lot of things going on...
今日はねねが少しでもみんなに元気をあたえられるように頑張って練習をしてきました
...but today, Nene has been practicing hard so that I can give you all even just a little bit of energy.
皆さんどうでしたか？
How was it, everyone?
ねねのおかげでちょっとでも元気が出たらいいな、ありがとうね！
I hope you feel a bit better thanks to Nene. Thank you!
はーい！というわけで、スパークルをお聞きいただきました！ありがとう！
Yes! And with that, you've listened to "Sparkle"! Thank you!
いや、おまるんに1回だけあのペラペラで前の服だった時に、1回連れてきてもらったことがあったんだけど
You know, Omarun brought me here once before when I was in my old outfit and it was a flat stage...
ねね自体がね、ねねが自分の足でこのステージを踏むのは初めてだから、今めっちゃ嬉しい気持ちでいっぱいです、やったー！
...but for Nene herself, stepping onto this stage with my own feet is a first, so I'm just filled with so much happiness right now. Yay!
さてさて、時間もね、残りわずかとなりました。
Now then, our time is also running short.
みんなラスト次が一曲になるんですけど、
Everyone, the next song will be the last one,
何の曲だと思う？みんな。
what song do you think it is? Everyone.
まだ一曲だけさ、ほら、ねねといえばさ、ほら、
There's still one more song, you know, when you think of Nene...
ねねがいっぱい目のあの曲が、あの曲があるでしょみんな。あの、あの曲だよ。
That song with lots of "Nene"s, that song is coming up. That one, you know?
みんな、もう知ってる、知ってる、あの曲だよ。
Everyone already knows it, you know it, that song.
あれをね、最後にみんな元気よく歌って、元気にこのライブを締めたいと思いますので、
I want to sing that last one energetically with everyone and close this live show with a bang,
皆さん、よかったら最後の一曲なので最後まで聞いていってください。
so everyone, please listen to this last song until the very end.
今日は見てくれてありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for watching today.
それでは、最後の曲、聞いてください。
Well then, please listen to the final song.
ねねねねねねねねねねねねねね大爆走！
Nenene Nenene Nenene! Daibakuso!
なななな ななちゃんじゃなくて
Na-na-na-na, I'm not Nana-chan
にににに ににじゃなくて
Ni-ni-ni-ni, I'm not Ni-ni
ぬぬぬぬ ぬぬちゃんじゃなくて
Nu-nu-nu-nu, I'm not Nu-nu-chan
のののの ののじゃなくて
No-no-no-no, I'm not No-no
うー！ねね！
Wooo! Nene!
ねね！
Nene!
よいしょ よいしょ よいしょ よいしょ
Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho
ねね！
Nene!
よいしょ よいしょ よいしょ よいしょ
Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho
こんねねー 異世界から来ました
Kon-Nene! I came from another world.
オレンジ担当 桃鈴ねねです（ねねち！）
I'm Momosuzu Nene, the one in charge of orange (Nene-chi!)
異世界から来ました アイドル志望の
I came from another world, as a rookie VTuber
新米VTuber（ねねち！）
who wants to be an idol (Nene-chi!)
まぁとにかく明るく行きましょう
Well, anyway, let's keep it bright.
ちょっとくらい緊張したって 滑ったって
Even if you're a bit nervous or slip up,
「うわー」って感じにさ やってやっていこう（いぇー！）
just go with a "Woah!" feeling and let's do it (Yeah!)
諦めの悪さは長所だね
Being a bad loser is a good point, right?
ねねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね
Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene
変なこともあるけど
Strange things happen sometimes, but
悔しいこともあるけど大丈夫
there are frustrating things too, but it's okay.
今日も明日もしっかりおめかしして
I'll dress up properly today and tomorrow too,
いつかはきっと スーパーねねち！（ついてきて！）
and one day I'll surely be Super Nene-chi! (Follow me!)
ねねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね
Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene
ねねね プレイゴー！
Nenene, Play go!
ねねね 全開でいこう！
Nenene, let's go at full throttle!
思い切りやれば なんとかなるよ
If you give it your all, things will work out somehow.
ポンコツだっていい 誤字ったっていい
It's okay to be clumsy, it's okay to make typos.
ただ駆け抜けていこうよ
Let's just keep running through it.
ね！ね！ね！ね！大爆走！
Ne! Ne! Ne! Ne! Daibakuso!
ねね！
Nene!
よいしょ よいしょ よいしょ よいしょ
Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho
ねね！
Nene!
よいしょ よいしょ よいしょ よいしょ
Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho
野菜ジュースと炭酸とお菓子揃えて準備OK
Vegetable juice, soda, and snacks all ready, preparation OK.
でも朝は苦手 夜も苦手 やっぱり睡眠第一だよね
But I'm not a morning person, nor a night person. Sleep is the most important, after all.
ねねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね
Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene
たくさんの人に愛されたい（チュッチュッチュッ！チュッチュッチュッ！）
I want to be loved by many people (Chu chu chu! Chu chu chu!)
大好きなみんなに愛されたい（チュッチュッチュッ！チュッチュッチュッ！）
I want to be loved by all of you I love (Chu chu chu! Chu chu chu!)
そしたらなるんだ ハイパーねねち！（やってやって！）
Then I'll become Hyper Nene-chi! (Go for it!)
ねねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね
Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene
ねねね プレイゴー！
Nenene, Play go!
ねねね 全開でいこう！
Nenene, let's go at full throttle!
歌は誰にも 負けたくないんだ
I don't want to lose to anyone when it comes to singing.
大きな声で 朝が来る前に
With a loud voice, before morning comes,
ちょっとトイレ行ってくるね（レッツ・ゴータイム！）
I'm just going to the restroom for a bit (Let's go-time!)
みんなー！今日はありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you for today!
こんなにいっぱいの人たちが見てくれて幸せー！
I'm so happy so many people are watching!
これからもねねのこと、見ててねー！
Please keep an eye on Nene from now on too!
なななな ななちゃんじゃなくて
Na-na-na-na, I'm not Nana-chan
にににに ににじゃなくて
Ni-ni-ni-ni, I'm not Ni-ni
ぬぬぬぬ ぬぬちゃんじゃなくて
Nu-nu-nu-nu, I'm not Nu-nu-chan
のののの ののじゃなくて
No-no-no-no, I'm not No-no
ただいまー！
I'm back!
最後に ねねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね
For the last time, Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene
ねねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね
Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene Nenene
ねねね プレイゴー！
Nenene, Play go!
ねねね 全開でいこう！
Nenene, let's go at full throttle!
思い切りやれば なんとかなるよ
If you give it your all, things will work out somehow.
ポンコツだっていい 誤字ったっていい
It's okay to be clumsy, it's okay to make typos.
ただ駆け抜けていこうよ
Let's just keep running through it.
ね！ね！ね！ね！大爆走！
Ne! Ne! Ne! Ne! Daibakuso!
それじゃあみんな本当にまたねねー！
Well then everyone, see you again Nene!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
桃鈴ねね
ねねいろらいぶ
NENEIRO LIVE
Momosuzu Nene
Neneiro Live
NENEIRO LIVE
3D Streaming
6/12(sat) 20:00(JST) START